

Victor Lebecq 11/10/1999 Grenoble, France

React Web Developer

+336 47 93 63 08 victor.lebecq.pro@gmail.com linkedin/victor-lebecq github/pommito

React Web Developer with two years of freelance experience. Over this period, I have delivered robust web solutions for direct clients, addressing concrete business challenges. I have also worked with agencies and companies, giving me comprehensive experience with technologies such as Reactjs, Wordpress, and Astro.js.

Technical skills

Langages Javascript / TypeScript, PHP, Html, Css

Frontend Wordpress, React, Astrojs, Redux, Design system (Tailwind, Sass, Styled Components),

Backend Laravel, NodeJS, Express, Rest API, MySQL

Tools Git, Docker, Vercel, Vite, Figma, Jest, Insomnia

Project management Kanban, SCRUM, Agile methods

Communication Français (natif), Anglais (C1), Espagnol (B1)

Experiences

Freelance wordpress developer

Titan Informatique - Digital agency - in remote

- Creation and development of WordPress websites for new clients (showcase, e-commerce, catalog).
- Management and maintenance of the company's existing client website portfolio.
- Direct client interaction and implementation of personalized follow-up.

Freelance web developer

Jan. 2023 - Current

Mar. 2024 - Nov. 2024

Digit'Alp - Personnal company

- Creation and development of websites for direct clients (showcase, e-commerce).
- Technical interventions on behalf of web agencies using various programming languages.
- Management and maintenance of an existing portfolio of client websites.

Digital marketing internship

Sept. 2022 - Sept. 2023

BVA Assurances - Insurances - Chambéry

- Creation of a website and visual identity.
- Development of the company's client portfolio.
- Implementation of a digital acquisition strategy.

Education

Formation développeur web et web mobile

O'clock - Certification BAC +2 - In remote

- Remote Training in Web and Mobile Web Development with RNCP Certification
- Learning and mastering various web languages (JavaScript, PHP).
- Specialization in front-end development with React.js.

Master Marketing Digital

CNAM AURA - Certification BAC +5 - Saint-Etienne

- Master's Degree in Marketing (Work-Study Program)
- Completed a thesis on the impact of climate change on the business plans of ski resorts.

Hobbies

- Alpine Skiing
- Freeski
- Ski Touring
- Table Tennis at a High Level (for 10 years)
- Travel
- Music
- Video Games

Oct. 2023 - Apr. 2024

Sept. 2021 - Sept. 2022